https://www.verdict.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy sets out how Verdict Media Limited collects and uses information from users (“User” or “you”) of our website and/or any website which is operated by Verdict Media Limited (“Verdict Media Limited”, “our”, “we” or “us”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Website and all products and services offered by Verdict Media Limited.
What Information Do We Collect?
We may collect the following information:
(a) personal information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Website, register on the Website, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Website. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Website anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website related activities.
(b) non-personal information about Users whenever they interact with our Website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Website, such as the operating system and the Internet Service Provider’s utilised and other similar information.
(c) cookies and log files may be used on our Website to enhance User experience. A cookie is a small text file written to an individual’s hard drive that contains the user ID. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies at being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Website may not function properly. You can find out more about the use of cookies and how you can remove them by going to http://allaboutcookies.org or http://www.cookiecentral.com.
How we use collected information
Any personal data that you give us will be treated with the utmost care and security. The personal data we collect is used to provide you with the service that you have requested or to respond to an enquiry that you have made.
Verdict Media Limited uses User personal information we have collected for the following purposes:
to personalise User experience: we may use information individually or aggregated to understand how our Users use the services and resources provided on our Website.
to improve our Website: we continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
to improve customer service: your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
to process transactions: we may use the information Users provide when placing an order to service that order, as well as provide relevant information about our other products. We do not automatically share this information with third parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service or when explicitly given permission by the User. The User can at any time change its preferences by contacting us via our Website.
to administer Website features: such as content, promotions and surveys and to send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them
to send periodic emails: the email address Users provide will be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their orders as well as (a) respond to their inquiries and requests or (b) provide relevant information about our other products.
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Website.
Third-party usage tracking analytics
In addition to our own usage analytics, we use several third-party services to process personal information for the purposes listed above. While some of the services listed beneath may not be enabled at any specific time, services we use include:
Google Advertising (Google LLC)We Google to serve advertisments and use cookies for ad personalisation and measurement.Privacy PolicyOpt-outUnited States (Privacy Shield compliant)
Service
Description
Privacy Policy
Opt-Out
Place of Processing
Google Analytics (Google LLC)
We use the data collected by Google Analytics to track and examine the use of
this application and to prepare reports on user activities.
Privacy Policy
Opt-out
United States (Privacy Shield compliant)
Permutive (Permutive Inc)
We use data collected by Permutive to track and analyse customer interactions with our website. User’s IP addresses are received and processed but raw IP’s are not stored.
Privacy Policy
Opt-out
United States (Privacy Shield compliant)
Facebook (Facebook Inc)
This Cookie is placed by Facebook. It enables us to measure, optimise and build audiences for advertising campaigns served on Facebook.
Privacy Policy
Opt-out
United States (Privacy Shield compliant)
Clearbit (Clearbit Inc)
We use Clearbit to resolve a company name from your IP address when possible
Privacy Policy
Opt-out
United States (Privacy Shield compliant)
User right to Opt-out
User’s right to Opt-out
If you do not want to continue to receive e-mail communications from us please let us know by sending an e-mail to unsubscribe@verdict.co.uk. Should you request that we amend or suppress records containing your personal data we will endeavour to do so as promptly as practical; however you may receive communications for a transitional period whilst we process your records.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Website. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Website and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Website is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.
Sharing your personal information
Unless we are given explicit permission to do so; we do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal information. We may without consent share generic aggregated information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Website or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys.
List of our websites
verdict.co.uk
hydrocarbons-technology.com
offshore-technology.com
railway-technology.com
ship-technology.com
airforce-technology.com
cosmetics-technology.com
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Website that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Website, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our Website may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognise your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Changes/Updates to Privacy Policy
In order to keep up with changing legislation and best practice, we may revise this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Website. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Website. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contact us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at unsubscribe@verdict.co.uk or alternatively:
Data Protection Officer
Verdict Media Limited
John Carpenter House
John Carpenter Street
London EC4Y 0AN
United Kingdom
